question_data = [
    {"text": "A slug's blood is green.",
      "answer": "True"},
    {"text": "The loudest animal is the African Elephant.",
      "answer": "False"},
    {"text": "Approximately one quarter of human bones are in the feet.",
      "answer": "True"},
    {"text": "The total surface area of a human lungs is the size of a football pitch.",
      "answer": "True"},
    {"text": "In West Virginia, USA, if you accidentally hit an animal with your car, you are free to take it home to eat.",
      "answer": "True"},
    {"text": "In London, UK, if you happen to die in the House of Parliament, you are entitled to a state funeral.",
      "answer": "False"},
    {"text": "It is illegal to pee in the Ocean in Portugal.",
      "answer": "True"},
    {"text": "You can lead a cow down stairs but not up stairs.",
      "answer": "False"},
    {"text": "Google was originally called 'Backrub'.",
      "answer": "True"},
    {"text": "Buzz Aldrin's mother's maiden name was 'Moon'.",
      "answer": "True"},
    {"text": "No piece of square dry paper can be folded in half more than 7 times.",
      "answer": "False"},
    {"text": "A few ounces of chocolate can to kill a small dog.",
      "answer": "True"}
]

question_data_2 = {"response_code":0,
                   "results":
                   [
                       {"type":"boolean",
                        "difficulty":"medium",
                        "category":"Animals",
                        "question":"The Platypus is a mammal.",
                        "correct_answer":"True",
                        "incorrect_answers":["False"]
                        },
                       {"type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","category":"Entertainment: Japanese Anime &amp; Manga","question":"No Game No Life first aired in 2014.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","category":"Geography","question":"New Haven is the capital city of the state of Connecticut in the United States.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"hard","category":"Science &amp; Nature","question":"The value of one Calorie is different than the value of one calorie.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"hard","category":"Science &amp; Nature","question":"It was once believed that injecting shark cartilage into people would prevent them from contracting cancer.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","category":"Science &amp; Nature","question":"An exothermic reaction is a chemical reaction that releases energy by radiating electricity.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","category":"Art","question":"Pablo Picasso is one of the founding fathers of &quot;Cubism.&quot;","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","category":"Science &amp; Nature","question":"Water always boils at 100&deg;C, 212&deg;F, 373.15K, no matter where you are.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","category":"Entertainment: Video Games","question":"In Half-Life 2, if you play the zombies&#039; speech in reverse, they actually speak coherent English.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","category":"General Knowledge","question":"&quot;Buffalo buffalo Buffalo buffalo buffalo buffalo Buffalo buffalo.&quot; is a grammatically correct sentence.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]}]}